The Christmas Ringer is a music, drama film directed by Patricia Cuffie-Jones.
When a popular R&B singer's career takes a turn, she returns home for the holidays and ends up
directing her family's church choir to help them win a Christmas competition.
Nicole, played by Trenyce.
Building Manager, played by Roger Anthony.
Grady, played by Jarrett Michael Collins.
Anne, played by Arischa Conner.
Roland, played by Quinnes Dammond Parker.
Jorge, played by Adrian Hernandez.
Merritt Patterson is a Canadian actress.
She had her breakout role in 2013 on the ABC Family Pretty Little Liars spin-off
series Ravenswood then went on to play Ophelia Pryce in the E!
television series The Royals (2015).
Merritt has starred in a number of holiday films for
Hallmark Channel and Great American Family.
In 2021, Patterson was cast opposite Dave Franco, Daryl Hannah,
and Bill Murray in Quibi's miniseries The Now.
The tone is emotional.